Ahmed Ali Gawish

Front-End Developer

▲ AhmedGawish22@gmail.com

**** 01064880594

≡ 5 Sep 2001 **♀** Kafr Elsheikh - Egypt

https://github.com/ahmedgawish10

in https://linkedin.com/Ahmed-Gawish

Summary

I am a Passionate Front-end developer with expertise in HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JavaScript, ReactJs, NextJs and Angular. Gained Skills in creating responsive web designs as a trainee in (ITI), gained ability to collaborate effectively within a team. Committed to continually updating skills. Familiar with backend technologies such as PHP, MySOL

Education

Bachelor of Technology and Information Systems, PortSaid University Cumulative Grade(GPA): Very Good with Honors

2019 - 2023

Work Experience

Front-End Developer at Rukn

May, 2024 - Present

- August, 2021 Present Front-End Developer on Upwork (Freelancer) Convert Figma designs into responsive websites using HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind, JavaScript, ReactJs
- Fullstack Web Developer at ITI January, 2024 - May, 2024 develop web pages and build responsive websites using HTML3, CSS3, JS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Angular, PHP, MySQL, Laravel, WordPress Others: Docker, Git, Linux, CLI
- Fundamentals Web Development Summer Training at ITI July, 2022 August ,2022 Create and design responsive websites using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap

Technical Skills

Front-End

• HTML5

- Tailwind CSS
- ReactIS
- TypeScript

- CSS3
- Material UI
- Redux
- Formik & Yup

- SASS
- JavaScript
- NextIS
- React-hook-form & Zod

- BootStrap5
- jQuery
- Angular
- Git & GitHub

- Back-End
 - PHP
 - My SQL
- Strapi (CMS)
- Laravel
- Firebase
- NodeJS

Projects

♣ Graduation Project: Arduino Measure Diabetes

- **Grade**: Excellent
- **Description**: A sensor device inserted into the patient's arm for 14 days, which converts a signal to be received via Bluetooth to a mobile app for blood sugar monitoring.
 - Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap5, JavaScript, Reactjs
 - Arduino Product Website: Demo

Projects

• Next & Strapi

Al-Jewar Travel Agency App: Demo

Technologies: HTML - CSS- Tailwind - JavaScript - Next.js - i18Next

Courses Tech App: Code

A learning platform designed for seamless educational experiences, built with **Next.js** and **Strapi** for content management, authentication by **Clerk**, payment integration with **Stripe**.

Technologies: HTML - CSS - Tailwind - JavaScript - Next.js - Strapi - Clerk - Stripe - Cloudnairy

PHP & MY SQL

Job Portal App: Code

Job portal application designed to simplify the hiring process for organizations. This web-based solution facilitates job postings and candidate applications.

Technologies: HTML - CSS - PHP - MY SQL

React & Firebase

Portfolio: Demo

Dashboard-ABrand: Demo

Dashboard for managing an e-commerce website, allowing admins to add and manage products. **Technologies**: HTML - CSS - JavaScript - Material UI - React - Firebase Realtime Database.

■ E-commerce-ABrand: Demo

E-commerce website designed to sell a variety of electronics, books, and clothing, **Technologies**: HTML - CSS - TypeScript - Material UI - React - Redux Toolkit - Firebase.

■ E-commerce: Demo

E-commerce website for the medical industry, facilitating the sale of a variety of medical healthy products. The application ensures a smooth shopping experience for customers.

Technologies: HTML - CSS - JavaScript - React - Redux Toolkit - react slick carousel - REST API

Angular

■ E-commerce: Demo

e-commerce website using Angular with user authentication and lazy Loading for optimized performance. The application uses local storage, ensuring a seamless shopping experience.

Technologies: HTML - CSS -Bootstrap -JavaScript - Angular - REST API

IavaScript

■ E-commerce Website: demo

Personal Skills

- Good organizational, interpersonal and Communication skills.
- Strong attention to detail and ability to multitask effectively.
- problem solving and High flexibility in thinking.
- Time management skills.
- Self-study.

Languages

• Arabic mother tongue

English

conversational